Guide to the Lantern Slide Collection c. 1860-1942 PR 70
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: General Lantern Slides, 1
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters, 1858, 1831, 1850, 1909, 1880 (Box 79, 80, Item PR-070-0001-0328)
    Academy of Music at 14th Street and Irving Place--views with cars, carriages and façade, as well as gates from nearby apartment houses; Astor Place Theatre/Opera House showing surrounding area, as well as view of riot scene; Bowery Theater façade image wi
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters, interiors, 1863, 1859, 1833, 1850, 1888, 1761 (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0329)
    Academy of Music Russian Ball, Union Square, showing women and soldiers dancing; Academy of Music Union Meeting showing men and main speaker taking hats off; American Theatre, Bowery--Tom Rice doing his Jim Crow act in crowded theatre; Castle Garden--firs
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters--Castle Garden (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0330)
    View of Castle Garden from water showing ships, boats and skyline; "Great Fair" at Castle Garden with men and women lined up at entrance; View of men outside Castle Garden with façade.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters--Hippodrome (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0331)
    Drawings of Hippodrome with flags, tents, and crowds surrounding exterior, as well as horses, carriages and pedestrians.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters--National Theatre, 1840, 1836 (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0332)
    Architectural plans and renderings of Old and New National Theatres; Façade view with pedestrians.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Theaters--Park Theatre, 1821, 1798, 1785 (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0333)
    Park Theatre view of stage with actors and balconies; Park Theatre view towards stage; Park Theatre architectural drawing; Old American Company Park Theatre program for "Gamester" and "Love A-La-Mode."
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Transportation--Elevated Railroads, 1873 (Box 80, Item PR-070-0001-0334)
    Elevated Railroad tracks viewed going away from station through city buildings; L Station at 33rd Street with Dime Savings Bank in Background; Construction of L at 110th Street and 8th Ave view of massive curve; Harold Square and Cooper Square (aerial vie
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Transportation--Grand Central Depot, 1880, 1871 (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0335)
    Several aerial views of old Grand Central Depot surrounded by trolleys, pedestrians and carriages with views of surrounding buildings; View of Grand Central Depot in distance with 42nd Street railroad yard in foreground showing workers filling snowplow lo
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Transportation--Pennsylvania Station (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0336)
    Penn Station façade with view of cobblestone streets and street lamps.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Transportation--Pennsylvania Station, interiors, 1910 (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0337)
    Penn. Station Terminal viewed from above showing entrance, as well as people walking and waiting for trains, with clock in background.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Transportation--Railroads, trains (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0338)
    Train under Park Ave.
  - New York-NYC-Queens--Churches, 1919 (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0339)
    Quaker Meeting House in Flushing.
  - New York-NYC-Queens--Residences--Houses and Homes (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0340)
    Samuel A. Lawrence Home showing foliage and lawn; Morris Residence façade; Façade views of Sprong-Duryea House in Flushing.
  - New York-NYC-Queens--Schools and Colleges (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0341)
    P.S. 5 in Astoria façade view with fence and field; Fourth Ward School in Astoria--façade view with sidewalk and tree; Side view of Original Astoria school.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Cemeteries (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0342)
    Old Baptist burying ground.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Churches (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0343)
    Dutch Ref. Church in Tomkinsville.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Commercial Buildings--Factories (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0344)
    Old Woodlen Mill in Richmond with fence and lake in distance.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Commercial Buildings--Restaurants and Taverns (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0345)
    Near duplicates of Black Horse Tavern in New Dorp with trees, fences and view of front porch; Drawing of Bull's Head Tavern with smoking chimney and roosters in foreground; G. Bechtel Brewery and Tavern façade view with barrels and field.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Government and Public Buildings (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0346)
    Richmond County Hall façade view.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Government and Public Buildings--Courthouses (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0347)
    First County Courthouse showing signs for coal and court house.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Government and Public Buildings--Detention Facilities (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0348)
    Old Red Jail, Richmond, with pedestrian, trees and fence.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Richmond (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0349)
    Fort Richmond viewed from distance with river and trees; Fort Richmond view of hills and trees.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Government and Public Buildings--Institutions--Sailor's Snug Harbor (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0350)
    Two similar views of row of buildings surrounded by grass and trees, and showing a few pedestrians; Side view of Sailor's Snug Harbor with cow.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Hotels (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0351)
    Swan Hotel; St. Marks Hotel; Continental Hotel.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Industrial Facilities (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0352)
    Brittons Mill on Clove Lake with view of waterwheel and dam as well as lake.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Monuments and Statues (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0353)
    Vanderbilt Mausoleum façade view with surrounding foliage.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Parks and Squares (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0354)
    Marthing's Pond near Actor's Home showing shoreline and trees; Factory pond in West New Brighton viewed with surrounding houses.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Parks and Squares--Silver Lake, 1820 (Box 81, Item PR-070-0001-0355)
    Similar views of Silver Lake with fenced building; deer and pedestrians nearby.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Residences--Houses and Homes, 1917, 1688 (Box 81, 82, Item PR-070-0001-0356)
    Latourette House in Richmond County showing façade with collapsed roof and missing doors; Cornelius Vanderbilt residence in Tomkinsville--façade showing steps and columns, as well as fence around property and trees; Tyler Mansion in West Brighton showing
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Residences--Houses and Homes--Billiopp House (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0357)
    Façade of Christopher Billopp House in Tottenville before 1688 in watercolor by T.O. Fraenkel, 1917; Billopp House showing family standing in front, as well as chickens and a turkey; hand-colored view of façade.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Residences--Houses and Homes--Fountain Homestead (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0358)
    Fountain Homestead original and remodled versions showing fences, trees, lawns, sidewalks and streets, as well as young woman leaning against log fence; view of façade with advertisement for clothing company, view of street and street lamp, as well as oth
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Schools and Colleges (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0359)
    Richmond Borough High School P.S. 1--façade view with pedestrians entering building; Curtis High school viewed with two boys standing in front.
  - New York-NYC-Staten Island--Streets (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0360)
    Old Post Road in Richmond showing fence, hill and tree line, as well as unpaved road.
  - New York-Stony Point (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0361)
    Images of Stony Point, including an artificial pond, and views north and south from Stony Point.
  - New York-Ticonderoga--Residences--Houses and Homes, 1755 (Box 82, Item PR-070-0001-0362)
    Mostly unlabeled hand-painted views of Ticonderoga houses, interiors and exteriors, and the King's Garden gate.
  - New York-West Point--Constitution Island, 1935, 1917, 1918 (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0363)
    Images of Constitution Island, including Warner House, Revolutionary War Ruins, Railroad tracks, view from West Point, bridges, and a meeting of the Constitution Island Association.
  - New York-West Point--Parks and Squares (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0364)
    Trophy Park image with canons.
  - North Carolina (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0365)
    St. Paul's Church in Edenton.
  - Pennsylvania (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0366)
    Phil. Carpenter's Hall; Philadelphia Library; Historical Society of Pennsylvania; Independence Hall; Upper Makefield Washington Headquarters; St. John's Church, York, Pa.; Old St. David's, Radmor; Old Pearson house in Darby, home of Darby Library Co.; Ger
  - Rhode Island (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0367)
    Old State House, Newport; Jeshuat-Israel Synagogue; St. Paul's; Kingston Library; Taylor House doorway.
  - South Carolina, 1909, 1922 (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0368)
    St. James Parish, Goose Creek, Charleston, S.C.; Charleston Library Society.
  - Utah (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0369)
    Mormon Tabernacle
  - Vermont, 1914 (Box 83, Item PR-070-0001-0370)
    Brookfield Town Library with man standing in foreground; Town Hall.
  - Virginia, 1910 (Box 84, Item PR-070-0001-0371)
    College of William and Mary and Hall of Burgesses of Virginia; Statue of Baron de Bottetourt; Libby Prison; Jeff. Davis Residence in Richmond; Mt. Vernon; Jefferson's Home in Charlottsville; House of Col. William Byrd; Yorktown Monument; Flower Garden at
  - Washington (Box 84, Item PR-070-0001-0372)
    Columbia River with mountain train passage.
- Series II: Songs, 2
  Scope and Contents Note
  Lantern slides which illustrate a song lyric. The song title, when known, is listed below.
  - Baby Face (6) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0001)
    Scott and Van Altena, 59 Pearl Street, New York
    couples, rowboats, bees, hearts, garden paths, gazebos, engagement rings, chains, photographs, pianos, books
  - Belong To Me (2) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0002)
    jams, berries, girls, couples, men
  - Bessie Dear (Sweet Bessie Dear?) (1) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0003)
    Metropolitan Lantern Slide Company, 51 West 28th Street, New York
    text
  - Bobb'n Up and Down (2) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0004)
    couples, oceans, suns, shells
  - By the Old Oaken Bucket, Louise (15) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0005)
    text, grass, fall leaves, wells, swings, moons, buckets, carriages, pitcher, waters, couples
  - Bygone Days (1) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0006)
    money, couples, hands
  - By the Silv'ry Rio Grand (1) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0007)
    St. Loius Calcium Light Co., 516 Elm St.
    trains, shops, railroad tracks
  - City of Sighs and Tears (1) (Box 84, Item PR-070-0002-0008)
    couples, fences, water fountains, trees hats, parks
  - College Boys (1) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0009)
    boys, flags, sports, hats, grass
  - Curfew Shall Not Ring To-Night (10) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0010)
    women, men, canes, hats, ladders, belltowers, swords, armor
  - Daddy Has a Sweetheart (and mother is her name) (1) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0011)
    pictures, frames, parents, daughters, roses
  - Dolly Dear (17) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0012)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York: c1907
    text, soldiers, couples, vines, paths, swords, docks, battleships, oceans, instruments, bands, searchlights, bells, weddings
  - Down in Melody Lane (1) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0013)
    hearts, guitars, bridges, couples
  - Dreami…(remainder is cut off) (2) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0014)
    Harry F. Stains Company, 713 North 41st Street, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
    bows, fans, instruments, couples, gladiolas
  - Dreams Just Dreams (1) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0015)
    sunsets / sunrises, girls, clouds
  - Fascinating Ragtime Glide (1) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0016)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York: 1909
    candies, shops, hotels, couples
  - Fiddle Dee Dee (3) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0017)
    fiddles, musicians, sheet music, rings, couple, goatees
  - Finest May (11) (Box 85, Item PR-070-0002-0018)
    couples, umbrellas, stone walls, peaches, photographs, oranges, moons, hearts, forests, grapes, bows, pentagons, lakes, swings, rowboats
  - Garden of Love, The (Take Me Back To?) (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0019)
    mirrors, umbrellas, couples, roses
  - Georgia (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0020)
    houses, paths, trees
  - Ghost of Violin (or The Ghost of the Violin) (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0021)
    violins, masks, swords, mugs, hourglasses, pots
  - Give me a small town Sweetheart (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0022)
    sunflowers, couples
  - Go 'Way Mistah Moon (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0023)
    wood, telescopes, couples
  - Golden Rod Flower of Liberty (16) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0024)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York: c1908
    text, flags, capital buildings, fields, golden rods, Uncle Sam, fences, mountains, roads, cows, couples, houses, vases
  - Good By All (2) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0025)
    railroads, luggage, daisies, hearts, parents, children
  - Good Old U. S. A., The (6) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0026)
    Scott and Van Altena, 478 West 145th Street, New York
    text, windows, mantles, fathers, sons, flags, crowds, police, marching bands, instruments, conductors, capitals
  - He Never Even Said Good-bye (2) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0027)
    Harstn and Company, 138 East 14th Street, New York
    Afro-Americans, alcohol, dining rooms, children, parents, mirrors, mantles
  - Hearts and Eyes (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0028)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, 1215 Broadway, New York
    balconies, couples, parties, windows, doors, roofs
  - Humming Bird (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0029)
    nests, girls, costumes
  - I Want Someone (to Flirt with Me? Or to Love Me?) (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0030)
    couples, rocks, rubies
  - I Want to Be in Dixie (4) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0031)
    railroads, luggage, parasols, clouds, moons, palms, frames, oceans, cars, girls
  - I will miss you girlie mine (1) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0032)
    Scott and Van Altena, 59 Pearl Street, New York; 5 Buffalo Slide Exchange
    letters, desks, envelopes, couples, stamps
  - I'm Afraid to Come Home (In the Dark?) (3) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0033)
    Simpson's Celebrated Slides: A. L. Simpson, New York: c
    snow, houses, steps, porches, alcohol, tea, bandages, nightgowns, pillows
  - I'm Trying So Hard to Forget You (15) (Box 86, Item PR-070-0002-0034)
    Scott and Van Altena, New York; 5 Buffalo Slide Exchange
    text, girls, gazebos, roses, pianos, paintings, couples, parasols, steps, flowers, moon, lake, canoe, statues, pillows, cities, carriages, nights
  - If I Had a Girl Like You (1) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0035)
    carriages, horses, moons, streets
  - In the Good Old Fashioned Way (21) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0036)
    Chicago Transparency Company, 84 Adams Street
    text, houses, fireplaces, couples, fences, yarn, knitting, paths, tracks, gates, paintings
  - In the Land of Harmony (1) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0037)
    sheet music, couples, conductors, violins
  - It Was Your Pleasing Smile (16) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0038)
    text, walls, parasols, trees, rivers, birds, moons, roses, balconies, lilies, oceans, hearts, houses, steps, fans, frames
  - It's always June when you are in love (1) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0039)
    birds, snow, trees
  - It's You, Pal (1) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0040)
    gardens, paths, birds, couples, steps
  - Just One Dearie (14) (Box 87, Item PR-070-0002-0041)
    Harry F. Stains Company, 2220-2222 Federal Street, Camden, New Jersey
    photographs, steps, houses, hammocks, couples, ghosts, gazebos, moons, walls, fireplaces, lakes, windows, trees
  - Just One Sweet Girl (6) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0042)
    dogs, couples, roses, steps, sunsets, parasols, birds, fences, ;lakes, reflections, grapes
  - Just Tell Her That I Loved Her Too (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0043)
    tents, guns, soldiers
  - Kentucky Sue (or Sweet Kentucky Sue) (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0044)
    Scott and Van Altena, 59 Pearl Street, New York; 9 Buffalo Slide Exchange
    safes, couples
  - Lady Love (12) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0045)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York: c1909 (Sets 1-2); Excelsior Slide Company, 138 East 14th Street, New York (Set 3)
    houses, gazebos, couples, bridges, parasols, porches, lakes, trees, fields, paths, horses, fences, rivers
  - Leav's Were Falling (3) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0046)
    couples, roses, fans, canes, clocks, walls, frames, palms
  - Let me prove my love to you, (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0047)
    Levi's Perfection Slides, 24 Union Square East, New York
    couples, daisies,
  - Let's build a bridge from your heart (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0048)
    hammocks, girls, roses, fans, pillows
  - Let's Buzz (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0049)
    pears, couples
  - Life Boat (7) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0050)
    waves, ocean, umbrellas, life vests, life boats, drowning
  - Live in My Heart (1) (Box 88, Item PR-070-0002-0051)
    umbrellas, couples
  - Lonesome (16) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0052)
    text, stone, houses, parasols, paths, fences, pillows, couches, grapes, books, lamps, fireplaces, trees, couples, curtains, reflections, rowboats, rivers, mountains
  - Lonesome Land (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0053)
    Excelsior Slide Company, 138 East 14th Street, New York
    couples, paths, vines
  - Longest Way Round (Is the Sweetest Way Home) (3) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0054)
    streams, trees, parasols, couples, waterwheels, fences, fields
  - Loving Man (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0055)
    hearts, girls, boys, ribbons
  - Mammy's Shuffling Dance (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0056)
    Scott and Van Altena, 59 Pearl Street, New York; St. Louis Calcium Light Co, 516 Elm St.
    Afro-Americans, children, dance, ships, docks
  - Mary (2) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0057)
    benches, forests, couples, rocks
  - Mary Was My Mother's Name (13) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0058)
    roses, bonnets, houses, porches, paths, mothers, daisies, trees, couples, girls, lakes, text, pipe organs, wood, tulips, sun, hearts, roses, birds, hearts, sons
  - Mary You're a Big Girl (2) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0059)
    flowers, trees girls, couples, streams, fences, rocks
  - Mello-Cello Melody (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0060)
    sheet music, instruments, couples, musicians
  - Mid the Green Fields of Virginia (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0061)
    J. D. Cress: c1899
    houses
  - Mississippi Dippy Dip, The (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0062)
    drums, costumes, dances, masks, clowns
  - Mother Old and Gray (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0063)
    frames, girls, crowns, clovers
  - My Alabama Rose (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0064)
    trains, smoke
  - My Beautiful Rose (3) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0065)
    roses, baskets, vines, couples, parasols, palms, paths, frames
  - My Beautiful Rose (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0066)
    ships, palms, ocean
  - My Little Georgia Rose (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0067)
    dogs, porches, canes, writing, rocking chairs
  - My Little Lovin' Sugar Babe (10) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0068)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York
    trees, paths, couples, moons, lakes, sweets, roses, churches, clocks, steeples,
  - My Love is Greater than the World (1) (Box 89, Item PR-070-0002-0069)
    Lake Shore Film and Supply Song Slide Department
    couples, steps, gates, fences, proposals
  - My Martha Jane (15) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0070)
    text, groups, brides, grooms, weddings, churches, bells, priests, porches, fireplaces, spinning wheels, homes, children, parents, books, kisses, photographs, tissues, deaths
  - Nearer, My God, To Thee (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0071)
    sheet music
  - Night and Day (2) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0072)
    pillows, girls, hearts, stars, roses, lockets
  - Nobody's Little Girl (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0073)
    Scott and Van Altena, 59 Pearl Street, New York: c1907
    postmen, teddy bears, cars, letters, mail
  - Oh That Loving Man? (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0074)
    DeCommerce Lantern Slide Company, 46 East 14th Street and 47 East 13th Street, New York
  - Oh Why Why (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0075)
    roses, ribbons, couples
  - Oh You Circus Day! (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0076)
    money, ticket booths, couples, parasols
  - Oh You Little Bear (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0077)
    pearls, jewels, jewelry boxes, girls, gold
  - Put Your Arms Around Me, Honey (I Never Knew Any Girl Like You) (5) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0078)
    text, lakes, grass, trees, moons, cupids, angels, girls, lockets, couples, paths, gardens
  - Ragtime Dream, The (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0079)
    girls, oceans, beds, shoes, feet, nightcap, pillows
  - Ragtime Major Sam (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0080)
    drums, marching bands, crowds, musicians, conductors, police, dwarfs
  - Ragtime Violin (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0081)
    violins, parties, dancing
  - Rainbow (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0082)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120 West 31st Street, New York: c1908
    paths, forest
  - Red Red Rose (6) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0083)
    roses, porches, girls, paths, gardens, benches, birds
  - Rock of Ages (5) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0084)
    Joseph Krewson, Mt. Ephram, N.J.
    crosses, rocks, women
  - Send for Me (1) (Box 90, Item PR-070-0002-0085)
    text, phonographs, boys
  - She Was Bred in Old Kentucky (11) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0086)
    text, girls, couples, mothers, porches, windows, houses, cemeteries, streams, children, house interiors, fences,
  - Sit on the Moon (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0087)
    moons, faces, girls, baskets, balloons, bows
  - Somebody is Getting It (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0088)
    photographs, couples, cars, lamps, desks, moons
  - Soul Kiss, The (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0089)
    soldiers, swords, gypsies, villas
  - Star Spangled Banner (National Anthem of U. S.) (3) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0090)
    T. H. McAllister Company, 49 Nassau St., New York
    text, flags, sun, clouds, eagles, rocks
  - Stay In Your Own Backyard (6) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0091)
    J. D. Cress: c1901
    Afro-Americans, fences, barrels, houses, children, boys, mothers, axes, wood, brooms, paths, crying, fights, hugs
  - Stop! Stop! Stop! (Come over and love me some more) (4) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0092)
    bees, couples, clocks, canes, lamps, guitars, pillows
  - Story of the Signal Man, The (9) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0093)
    railroads, railroad tracks, family, children, man, woman, railroad signal towers, windows, writing, clocks, railroad accidents, railroad stations, birds, spinning wheels, house interiors, text
  - Summer Girl, The (7) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0094)
    Elite Lantern Slide Company, 207 West 34th Street, New York
    text, rowboats, lakes, couples, parasols, paths, sailboats, seas, bridges, gazebos, beaches, oceans
  - Sweetheart (3) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0095)
    Alf. L. Harst & Co., 138 East 14th Street, N.Y.
    couples, trees, rocks, wells, footbridges, rivers
  - Take Me to Roseland Oh My Beautiful Rose (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0096)
    flowers, canes, couples
  - Sweetheart (Rem.) (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0097)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120 West 31st Street, New York: c1909
    paths, snow
  - Take Me Up (With You ) Dearie. (1) (Box 91, Item PR-070-0002-0098)
    DeWitt C. Wheeler, Inc., 120-122 West 31st Street, New York: c1909
    text, dirigibles, landscapes, couples